goproallaccess.com 2016-12-19

# Go Pro All Access

Thank you for visiting the Go Pro All Access ("GoProAllAccess.com") and reviewing our Page Privacy Policy. GoProAllAccess.com applies leading privacy practices and adheres to data stewardship principles in managing our user data. The data stewardship principles guiding our efforts include the following goals:

  * protection of user privacy
  * maintaining the confidentiality of user data
  * ensuring appropriate levels of security for user data

This Privacy Policy describes how GoProAllAccess.com applies these principles to the handling of personal information you provide to us via a GoProAllAccess.com

We understand that your privacy while using our service is important, especially when conducting business or providing sensitive personal information. This Notice will govern our Privacy Policy for users of this Site, whether or not a transaction of any sort is conducted while being serviced.

Personal information may include your name, email and home address, phone numbers, social security number and/or other information that identifies you personally, and is handled according to privacy regulations.

### Key Features our Privacy Policy includes:

  * Our Privacy Policy applies to all GoProAllAccess.com
  * We will not require you to register or provide personal information in order to use our service
  * GoProAllAccess.com does not collect personal information from Web users, unless the personal information is provided by you.
  * We use Web analysis tools (e.g. cookies) for limited uses authorized in this policy
  * Our Privacy Policy promotes the privacy, confidentiality, security and responsible handling of any information collected by GoProAllAccess.com over the phone or web.

### Your Personal Information

The information we learn from customers helps us to personalize and continually improve our customer service, while developing ways to improve your shopping experience at GoProAllAccess.com. 

### Information You Provide Us:

When you complete a Customer Profile Form or communicate with us via e-mail, letter, fax or phone, we receive and store the information you've provided. This information is basic, including: name, address, phone, fax and cell phone numbers, e-mail address and business information (if applicable). We use this information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, communicating with you and customizing future shopping for you.

### Third Party Vendors:

In addition to collecting your information, we have third party vendors who will also collect your information in order to provide the products and/or services you've requested (e.g. credit card companies, fulfillment companies, call centers, marketing companies and freight companies). In general, these companies are intermediaries acting solely to provide services related to your request. Most of these vendors have their own privacy policy to protect your information, and have access to personal information needed to perform their functions on behalf of Go Pro All Access, but may not use the same for other purposes

### Privacy

GoProAllAccess.com maintains your personal information in "system records". A system record is a file, database or program from which personal information is retrieved by name or other personal identifier.

We will use your information to process requests for services or information. Providing the information is generally voluntary, but if it is not provided, we may not be able to facilitate your application or registration. When information is required to process requests, you will be advised of required fields in GoProAllAccess.com online forms.

### Use of Cookies and Tracking Technologies

 **What is a Cookie?**

When you visit certain websites, our website will send a small piece of information called a "cookie" to your computer along with the Web page. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We can see what pages you click through, plus store items in your Go Pro All Access between visits. The 'Help' portion of the toolbar on most browsers will instruct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and/or how to disable cookies altogether.

**There are two kinds of cookies:**

  * A Session cookie is a line of text that is stored temporarily in your computer's random access memory (RAM). A session cookie is destroyed as soon as you close your browser.
  * A Persistent Cookie is a line of text that is saved to a file on your hard drive and is called up the next time you visit the Web site. This lets the Web site remember information about your previous visits and use of the Web site. Persistent cookies are generally not used by us unless there is a compelling and authorized reason for their use.

**We use session cookies in the following manner:**

  * Log-on and log-off process - you do not have to log-on and register to browse our site. If you decide to register with our site to use one of our online services, session cookies help with the log-on and log-off process. The cookies enable us to recognize your log-on ID when you log on so that we do not create a duplicate registration record for you.
  * Transactions and site usability - we use Session cookies to improve how you navigate through our Web site and conduct transactions. Session cookies are used to maintain your online session as you browse over several pages, or to store and enter information on a Web page so that you do not have to reenter the same information, repetitively. Session cookies may also be used to collect referral statistics when you click on a link to or from a GoProAllAccess.com Web page.
  * "IP address tracking": An "IP address" is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Sites, our servers log your IP address.

### Information Collected from Online Forms

Many of our programs have online forms. We will use the information you provide to respond to you or process a registration.

Please remember that automated responses are sent via email and may not be secure against interception across the internet. They may also remain as a permanent, retrievable record with your Internet Service Provider (ISP).

### Information from Other Sources

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Examples may include, but not be limited to, updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features offered by certain organizations; search results and links, including paid listings (such as Sponsored Links); and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers, and information from data providers.

### Children

Our website is directed to Adults 18 years and older who are looking to improve their network marketing abilities. Children and in particular children under the age of 13 should not be using our website. We do not collect personal information from Children under 13 years old.

### Security

In those instances where we secure your personal information GoProAllAccess.com uses industry standard encryption, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL). The connection icon area of your browser will change to "HTTPS" instead of "HTTP" when this security feature is invoked. Your browser may also display a lock symbol on the task bar at the bottom of your screen to indicate this secure transmission is in place. You should refer to the instructions for your particular Internet browser software to determine how to examine the security certificate from our Web site to verify the security of the connection.

For site security purposes and to ensure that GoProAllAccess.com Web sites remain available to all users, GoProAllAccess.com employs software programs to monitor network traffic in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Except for oversight or authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits other than those uses identified in this policy.

Unauthorized attempts or acts to either (1) access, upload, change, or delete information on this system, (2) modify this system, (3) deny access to this system, or (4) accrue resources for unauthorized use on this system, are strictly prohibited and may be considered violations subject to criminal, civil, or administrative penalties.

GoProAllAccess.com takes the security of all personally identifiable information we maintain very seriously. We implement various measures to protect the security and confidentiality of personally identifiable information. Such measures include access controls designed to limit access to personally identifiable information to the extent necessary to accomplish our mission. We also employ various security technologies to protect personally identifiable information stored in our systems. We test our security measures periodically to ensure that they remain operational.

All of our employees and partners are familiar with our security policy and practices. Your personal information is only accessible to a limited number of qualified people who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off when you finish using a computer.

This Web site provides access to other Web sites outside our control and jurisdiction. When you link to these Web sites, you leave our Web site and your communications with those Web Sites are no longer protected by our privacy policies. GoProAllAccess.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the non-GoProAllAccess.com sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy or terms and conditions of those sites to fully understand what information is collected and how it is used.

While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable for any such occurrences.

### Options

As discussed above, you always have the choice not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase with Go Pro All Access. If you do not want to receive e-mails or other mail from us, simply contact the Go Pro All Accesses offices and you will be removed from our mailing list.

### Trademarks and Service Marks

All Go Pro All Access logos, trademarks and service marks used on our websites, GoProAllAccess.com are trademarks, service marks or registered trademarks of Go Pro All Access in the U.S. and/or other countries. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics, and logos that appear on our website are the trademarks or service marks of their respective owners and are protected by US and international trademark laws and conventions. You are granted no right or license with respect to any of the aforesaid trademarks or service marks and any use of such trademarks or service marks is prohibited.

### Contact GoProAllAccess.com Privacy Service

Please let us know if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or use of your information. You can contact us at 1-866-576-6484. Your inquiry will be treated confidentially and will not be shared with third parties, except as necessary to respond to your inquiry.

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit GoProAllAccess.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Arizona. If you have any concern about privacy at GoProAllAccess.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

By using GoProAllAccess.com and our affiliated sites, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, your promise to comply with the representations you make and contained in the Privacy Policy, and your understanding of the scope and limitations of the protections provided under the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these policies, please do not use GoProAllAccess.com and our affiliated sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to our Privacy Policy will mean that you accept those changes.
